a lot of things to deal with um there
was a time where I was homeless um my
husband gave me an ultimatum to either
straighten up or get out um I had to
then leave my children behind because I
had nowhere to go um I spent a Time
homeless and it wasn't a very long time
but it was a hard time because at the
time I had a skin expander in my chest
and I was going through therapy um still
trying to keep my son out of the out of
the judicial system um it was it was it
was overwhelming and I'm so proud of
myself for being able to make it this
far um keeping up with the cushy um
doing comedy a lot of those things had
were were survival and coping things for
me the cushy saved me in one aspect that
I was so low at the time that I needed
the cushy to cushion me because I was
going through so much at that time that
that was the only positive I had to
focus on that got me through son was
going through that got me through my my
failing marriage that got me through
figuring out trying to figure out where
I was going to go on a limited amount of
income and keep a roof over my head
still going under surgeries
um I I don't know how I made it you know
what I mean like I feel like God has
something for me because I'm not in a
padded room I'm not in you know what I
mean I'm not like flipping cuckoo for
Cocoa Puffs um my son is about to come
home um me and my ex are getting along
well and we're able to co-parent our
children are doing well um I I have a
wonderful job now um I have a beautiful
apartment um I I have a car that I want
it's not the car that is it's not Brand
New by any means but it's the car that
I've always wanted um so I feel like I'm
like a a story of of hitting rock rock
bottom and just climbing my way to the
top and knowing that there is something
out there for me and that I have a lot
of time and I have um talent to change
my situation and it's changing you know
as we speak I've had a lot of good
things happen so I take the bitter with
the sweet you know at one point in my
life it was I I didn't know how I was
going to make it I was depressed enough
that I thought that my kids would be
better without me and now I I'm in a
such a different place that looking at
myself I'm proud now I'm proud of making
it through everything that I've endured
and that's the first time I've ever
really been proud of myself I have never
given myself credit and that so if if
you would
oh and we are
live hey what's up folks this is RP the
god AKA The Wizard AKA Ryan Perez the
the hustle own King and
today oh my God this is an honor to do
this because uh this is a personal
friend of mine but you know she's she's
going to be a big time celebrity you
guys are going to all know her name
pretty soon okay so I'm going to tell
you a little bit about you know Danny
redwind you know I don't want to say too
much because I'm going to actually get
into like asking her some questions and
getting her to tell her story herself
but you know here's here's a woman that
is a breast cancer
survivor who is now a comedian just
finished getting reconstructive
surgery okay she's gone through so
much and like you guys know you guys
have seen these videos you guys truly
understand what the hustle zone is all
about the hustle zone is about the
spirit of the entrepreneur you know we
may have different Lifestyles we may
have different different uh uh
backgrounds different genders uh
different sexual orientations however at
the end of the day we all have one thing
in common as entrepreneurs we all have a
story and this is really like you know
when she she just recently got the um a
reconstructive surgery and I was just
scrolling through my Instagram feed as
she was crying
and like I felt emotional I was
like you know because it was something
that you know like folks it's it it's
amazing it's amazing to see uh people go
after their dreams and go after goals
and there was times where she was saying
that she was praying that everything
goes goes well and I'm glad that it went
well so we're going to Welcome to the
house Miss Danny red one how's it going
Danny
uh oh oh you got
it hold on can can can we can you um are
you are you
live yeah press the button one more
time can you hear me now yeah I can hear
you now awesome so how are you doing
thank you for such a wonderful
introduction of course well it's well
deserved so uh you just finished just
tell us a little bit about I'm going to
cue your video in a few seconds here but
you know tell like how are you how are
you doing like you just you just got out
of surgery and yes I'm doing well I
actually uh had the surgery November 1st
and it is it was to be the final stage
of the Reconstruction um people don't
know when you have a a breast removed uh
you have to rebuild that breast and it
doesn't happen in one surgery it happens
in a series of surgeries so so um I had
had uh four surgeries prior that was
part of the
Reconstruction um removing the skin
expander putting in a implant doing fat
grafting um and that sort of thing um
and this stage was the final stage where
they actually possibly remov the the
implant put in a new one that fits
that's symmetric to your other side and
then do fat grafting so that's what I
had done um forour surgery wow expensive
it they did a lipos suction in my lower
back to take fat from that area to um
compensate for what was missing on the
reconstructed breast so I'm normal now
like I'm symmetrical I'm I'm still a
little firm on this side I'm still a
little sore I have to wear this surgical
garment for six to eight weeks but I'm
four weeks in so we're good to go there
I still have some soreness
but um I stopped taking medication a
couple of weeks ago so that's to be
expected um I just don't do well with
with narcotics yeah no doubt neither do
I they knocked me out so I stopped
taking those so I have been a little bit
sore but I'm doing well oh that's
awesome how many how many surgeries how
many surgeries have you had um like uh
total total yeah had seven surgeries
total holy moly yeah so that's been a
long long and and an emotional journey
and how do you feel now that you're free
that you you know like is this the last
surgery and do you think that it's G to
be the last and so how do you I'm
claiming it I'm claiming it to be the
last um fingers cross yeah I'm I'm I'm
happy where I am you know even if I lose
a little bit more fat than they
anticipate I'm fine with that um I feel
like I look the best that I have
throughout all of these surgeries so I'm
content with that I'm still cancer free
um I don't anticipate to go under the
ninth I'm I'm not that vain unless it
shriveled up like a great
then but I think I'm pretty good so so
we're gonna play a little bit of your
Clips just so that people can see how
talented you are just one second here so
we're just going to prop this up I don't
know if everyone can see
it so I was all excited I was like I'm
going to do them super long and I got in
the mirror and was like I look like
Millie
vanilla all I need is some green
contacts
and know
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's
AG I love you I love you too
honey but um I wanted to say I'm a
breast cancer survivor
y'all don't clap too fast I still drink
smoke weed
period don't judge
me yes but it's funny because um I was
just uh reading not too long ago that if
you is it like 20 minutes if you spend
20 minutes sucking titties so guys suck
more titties um you spend 20 minutes
sucking titties that lessens your chance
of getting breast cancer do you know
that hell if I would have known that I
would have had all my Partners
suck my titties for 20 minutes you know
that's 40 minutes of work though I mean
you
got all night you might as well suck
titty fck all night I mean you got to do
both right that's 40 minutes that's a
long session that's a whole
session I me gets it done in minutes so
I'm going to if you guys want to watch
the rest of that video I'll put the link
in the description that that was that
was hilarious um so I the first thing I
want to ask you is that
um you poke fun like the first thing you
know you poke fun of yourself and about
you having one boob yeah and you know
what you were saying to me earlier is
that you're really self-conscious so why
why would you go out out there and and
and make fun of
yourself I I felt like it was it was
part of my therapy um I needed to get it
out how I was feeling about a lot of
things that I was going through and I
didn't want it to be like a sad thing
because I I beat cancer I'm cancer free
like I don't want to make it seem like
it's a sad story because it's not right
you know there are a lot of funny things
that we go through and in and what we
think is a demise in our life um it felt
good for me to get up there and let
people know that I'm I'm human like I we
go through stuff you know and at the end
of the day being sad about it and making
yourself more miserable and depressed
wasn't it's it's not going to help
anything um you know when I when I
started doing comedy I I just became
cancer free and I made like a bucket
list and doing standup was something
that I always wanted to try but just you
know never thought about it enough to
actually try it um so so when I came
cancer free I was like I'm about to try
it I'm going to get up there and do it
and I got up there and at that time I
had a skin expander in my chest like I
didn't even I didn't have an implant and
um I patted my
bra look as normal as I could and I got
up on that stage and I told some jokes
and I had some people stand up and give
me a standing evation and I've been
hooked ever since um wow it's it's
therapeutic for me
because you know like I said in in the
darkest times you can find something
that that the light can shine on and
that that was that happened for me so
like with your career your your seems
like your your your your um your comedy
career has exploded I mean you've met so
many uh great people like can you name
drop for
everybody um yeah I've met some pretty
cool people I've met um I've met Dave
Chappelle for
one
baress um I've met cookie Hall which is
one of the bad girls of Comedy yeah um
I've met um so a lot of good locals like
uh Kool-Aid I've met Alex Thomas um I've
done a show with um uh Trev Houston who
is a BET Comic um I've done with AJ
Johnson and his brother peanut I've
opened up for them um DaNell Rollins
I've met on two different occasions wow
just recently I did a show with um a
upand cominging comedian he's on the the
Nick Canon wilding out show um DC
youngfly yeah so so yeah I've I've met
quite a few people and I've gotten a
really good rapport with with most of
the people that I've come in contact
with DC youngi he blazed me on stage and
it was the
funniest it was the funniest thing ever
but you know it's just
it's it's it's been a good experience
you know I can't I can't complain so
what makes what makes everyone fall in
love with Daniel red
wine um I don't know quite honestly
because I think I can be a bit Brash at
times I'm a little brutal a brutal
honest person but um I don't know maybe
my transparency you know I'm not ashamed
of my truth um I've been through a lot
um I have things that are going on on in
my life that I'm sure other people have
gone through if not going through
currently um and I don't sugar coat
anything I mean you know there's a lot
of good things in life but there's a lot
of shitty things that happen in life you
know it's all about how you deal with
those things that that person that you
are and I just decided not to be a punk
and a wimp about everything and still do
and enjoy life the way I see fit
throughout all of the mess I've been
through so so with um that being said so
not only you're a comedian you know
you're an entrepreneur and that's why we
have you on this on on the hustle Zone
because hustle Z's about inventors and
about people that want to make a change
you know and you have a product that I
recently saw on the news uh that you've
put together and I believe you're still
looking for investors Etc to help you
with that so can you tell us a little
bit about that yes it's called the cushy
and um it was something that I need
needed uh going through reconstructive
surgery um once I had my myectomy I was
down for about 12 weeks and when I went
back to work I had to wear the seat belt
I had to transport myself and uh wearing
the seat belt became very uncomfortable
um I kind of made up something at home
like a just a homemade little pillow
device that I was able to get onto my
seat belt and a girlfriend of mine
looked at me and said that's a product
that's something that you should
actually bu you should you know sketch
something out um I did I have a
girlfriend who is uh very good with
sewing she sews really well so I
basically put together the sketch and
she put together a prototype um after
tweaking it a little bit I submitted it
to a local Investment Group here in my
city and I was selected in three
days which is which is the fastest
anyone has ever been selected because
they give you 30 days to get pulled out
of the drawing and I was pulled out in 3
days um so then came the cushy um I
started they they gave me a small SE
Dent um and that that went really fast
because I think I
underestimated um how much it would cost
to test out materials um using different
materials to build a prototype um
finding out what tweaks the legal
standpoint of it getting a patent
started getting a lawyer get getting all
these things in place so that I could
protect my product um so the money went
really fast I still had a inventory
which was going slowly but surely but to
keep up um the the website and to keep
up the the the merchandise became more
of a challenge for me so I um without
further investment I just said I'm going
to keep plugging away because I still
have legal obligation over my so I'll
just keep pushing away at awareness I'll
keep pushing away at at making sales
here and there and that's what I've done
um over time um but it's it's been
really well received um I sell them at a
lot of um functions
fundraisers um and things of that nature
and I actually have a company that's
pretty interested in the cushy right now
um that's based out of Florida um the um
the guy that's the the head over the
company down there has been in constant
contact with me um in regards to helping
me out so um there is one lead you know
I'm not exclusive to anybody as of yet
but um I'm waiting for the right thing
to come along well it's going to happen
you know like the whole thing about
being an entrepreneur is taking action
and you know You' definitely most
definitely took action and you know you
defied a lot of odds so you know usually
I start the hustle Zone off with what is
your story um it's so important because
like I said before the story is is the
most important thing about the
entrepreneur a lot of a lot of people
look at entrepreneurs asking for stuff
like asking for jobs asking for money
you know asking for opportunity but no
one asks for our story you know so I
want to take this time to get to know
where we where we started and then how
we got here so tell us Danny what is
your story like if someone if you were
sitting in front of Barbara Walters
right now what would you
say my story is that I was a woman that
was lost and did not know where I wanted
to be and what I wanted to do and I was
diagnosed with breast cancer um that
changed everything for me because at the
time um my firstborn son was going
through some legal problems he got
hooked up with the wrong crowd um I was
having problems at my job um with
character issues because I was the only
brown girl in a corporate uh medical
field um where I was constantly
ridiculed and questioned about who I was
as a woman and as a person um I also
started the cushy um and my marriage was
failing uh I had a lot going on at the
time that I was
diagnosed I I survived through all of
that stuff I'm not only a survivor of
breast cancer but I had a lot of things
to deal with um there was a time where I
was homeless um my husband gave me an
ultimatum to either straighten up or get
out um I had to then leave my children
behind because I had nowhere to go um I
spent a Time homeless and it wasn't a
very long time but it was a hard time
because at the time I had a skin
expander in my chest and I was going
through therapy um still trying to keep
my son out of the out of the judicial
system um it was it was it was
overwhelming and I'm so proud of myself
for being able to make it this far um
keeping up with the cushy um doing
comedy a lot of those things had were
were survival and coping things for me
the cushy saved me in one aspect that I
was so low at the time that I needed the
cushy to cushion me because I was going
through so much at that time that that
was the only positive thing I had to
focus on that got me through son was
going through that got me through my my
failing marriage that got me through
figuring out trying to figure out where
I was going to go on a limited amount of
income and keep a roof over my head
still going under surgeries
um I I don't know how I made it you know
what I mean like I feel like God has
something for me because I'm not in a
padded room I'm not in you know what I
mean I'm not like flipping cuckoo for
Cocoa Puffs um my son is about to come
home um me and my ex are getting along
well and we're able to co-parent our
children are doing well um I I have a
wonderful job now um I have a beautiful
apartment um I I have a car that I want
it's not the car that is it's not Brand
New by any means but it's the car that
I've always wanted um so I feel like I'm
like a a story of of hitting rock rock
bottom and just climbing my way to the
top and knowing that there is something
out there for me and that I have a lot
of time and I have um talent to change
my situation and it's changing you know
as we speak I've had a lot of good
things happen so I take the bitter with
the sweet you know at one point in my
life it was I I didn't know how I was
going to make it I was depressed enough
that I thought that my kids would be
better without me and now i' I'm in such
a different place that looking at myself
I'm proud now I'm proud of making it
through everything that I've endured and
that's the first time I've ever really
been proud of myself I have never given
myself credit and that so if if you
would oh I think uh on hold on
okay okay I'm there we got some
technical difficulties everybody but you
know we still got the audio we're still
going to go through uh just one second
here
okay I can't hear Danny right now can
you see
me um I can't see you just one second
here let's
uh okay hold
on folks I'm so sorry but we have
technical difficulties
I think I just lost Danny here uh stay
tuned we're gonna we're going to get her
right
back we're going to get it right back
but that that is such an amazing
story ah holy cow um that is it's just
amazing what one person can
accomplish in such a small frame of time
you know and it just teaches you that
you know no matter what situation that
you're in that you never give
up you know and I'm going to I'm going
to call Danny right now we're going to
get it all set up again we're not going
to let this woman go like this is
amazing this is the Hustle onone Man
some things sometimes things happen so
it is what it
is we're going to get back and we're
going to get her back online oh There
She is again that's awesome we're we're
back so give give me one second I'm just
going to get your uh image propped up
there it seemed like I had some you know
these things are never uh you know I'm
on my phone yeah yeah it's all good we
got
you okay all
right my computer broke too so if
anybody want to
donate hey we need to if folks if you
guys have the power to set up a a
GoFundMe account you want to donate and
you know you want to help fund the the
the the cushy like go right on ahead
like make sure you guys add add add add
Danny redwind follow her you know she's
going to be a star one of these days you
guys going to know that she was on the
hustle
Zone you know because than for that into
existence I don't know if I really want
to be like a super big Superstar or
anything like that I like I think you're
going to be I think I think you're going
to be making a lot of money
though I think we all want that money
and I think you know most importantly we
want to be able to be safe we want to be
free we want to be at peace and after
listening to your story like you know
and understanding what held you together
like what would you have told you when
you were diagnosed with cancer sorry my
nose is itchy like uh I apologize what
what um what would you tell your former
self you know when you were diagnosed
like what would you have told
her I would have told told her that it's
going to be
okay um I didn't think that it was going
to be okay um I thought everything was
about to end for me I thought I I didn't
see what I have now um because there
were so many negative things going on
outside of the cancer itself I thought
the cancer was just the the nail and the
coffin you know what I mean like that's
no pun intended you know I felt like oh
c
this oh
seriously um so yeah I I definitely
would have told her that it's going to
be okay and to breathe and to allow
yourself to live your life um get some
direction decide what it is that you
love and do it um and I didn't see that
until
recently I mean even throughout all of
this you still go through it I think
that it's been in within the last year
or so that I have felt more empowered
just because I was still going through
it none of those problems resolved
overnight you know what I'm saying what
was the what was the Pinnacle for you
when did you realize that you know like
you're it like you're the the divorce
didn't resolve overnight like everything
lasted for a very long time I mean I
went through it for a while um and this
is with with and without without a car
with and without shelter with and
without a job like I went through it all
while I was going through surgeries um I
was so depressed at one time I didn't
work for almost six months I just laid
in my apartment and pretty much slept
because I was not motivated to do
anything I had just given up um and I
got tired of being that way because I
knew that that's that wasn't who I was I
knew that I wasn't that weak
um and I don't know exactly when it
changed or what lit a a match under me
but something changed and um I have been
going at it ever since wow I I I can I
when it when it comes to depression I
was depressed for maybe when I was in my
early teens I was uh or late teens 20s I
was depressed for about 5 years and I
stayed I stayed in home and I think a
part of me the reason why I work from
home even till today is a lot of habit
um habit that brought from the
depression because I was just going
through a lot personally and a lot of
metamorphosis and trying to figure
myself out and when you're when you're
going through
depression you're going through you feel
like it is
over yeah yeah you do like there's
nothing else that you can do you know
and for me I can resonate with with you
because there was just this one day I
said you know what I didn't pray to God
for like 5 years I was like man God
don't have nothing for me and then for
me I'm still not I'm not a religious
person but I just said you know I just
got to get through this and you know
God's going to get me through it soon as
I walk
outside Sun's
beaming I felt great and I felt like I
can start again and yeah you know do you
remember that day when you felt like
like like this is it like I'm going to
do this like yeah I was actually driving
down the highway one evening and I was I
I had a bad day that day and the sunset
it was just something about the way the
sky looked to me that day
that I just had a sense of comfort I had
a sense of I'm going to be okay and I
had a sense of get up off your ass and
do something because you are somebody
like this is not happening to you for no
reason this is something that you are
supposed to be a voice for and that is
when I started advocating um telling
people my story um I got quite a few
through I got quite a few um interviews
through some newspapers and through some
magazines I started to just share what I
was going through and when people
started writing me emails and started
following me and telling me that they've
been watching my story and they heard
about what was going on it was was such
a comfort to me because I felt like I
was letting people know that it's
okay it's okay to not are you there yeah
I'm still here okay it's it's okay to
not um know what is going to happen it's
okay to not understand where your future
is going to be what isn't okay is that
you just give up on it and say to hell
with it I'll settle for whatever comes
my way because none of us should none of
us should s none of us all of us should
be able to do the things that we love
and be able to be kind with one another
and help each other um I've had a lot of
people help me throughout my processes
and I wouldn't I don't think I would be
where I am if it wasn't for other people
um that that want wanted to help and
understood what I was going through and
had the means to help me I wouldn't be
where I am now not mentally not
spiritually you know not financially so
and speaking of the people that were in
your life and what about you know the
relationship that you had with your
ex-husband you know how did you overcome
that are you still do you still have
animosity uh with him over what had
happened in the past do you still have
scars how have you worked out that
relationship because you say that you
have a good relationship now but how has
that changed for you it's changed
because we have one thing in common and
and that's our
children um I love my kids more than
anything on this planet and I will do
anything to make sure that they are ha
happy and healthy um physically and
mentally it wouldn't it wouldn't have
done my children any good to see me and
their father not getting
along um regardless of our marriage not
working out I mean I I wanted things to
work out but I think after he gave me
that ultimatum and I was on my own I
think the resentment just buil you know
what I mean like it was it it wasn't it
didn't add to us getting closer it it
drew us further apart because I felt
betrayed in a sense right I'm going
through one of the hardest times in my
life right now and you put this in my
lap you make me feel unwanted um that
that is something that I think has been
hard for me to um consider getting back
with him um but we're going to always be
we're always going to conduct ourselves
as adults when it comes to our kids um
we don't argue around them we still have
family time together um we still
celebrate birthdays when we go to the
restaurant to eat as a family uh we just
had things giving together with my
ex-in-laws
um because at the end of the day it's
it's really not about us it about the
development of our children and that is
more important to me than than any
disagreement that we've ever had so and
like you know cuz I I I I can I can also
relate to you know being in a
relationship with someone that I loved
and you know being like being feeling
resentment after the breakup but
realizing that I I loved her so much
that I had to let her go I still love my
kids's father um I think it's
unfortunate that you know it happened
the way that it did um but it's it's
hard to go back I don't know if that
makes any sense yeah um because so much
has changed for me I'm I'm not the same
woman that he was with um I'm a lot more
confident I'm a lot more secure um you
know I was I was pretty submissive and
and passive at the time and now I'm like
the total
opposite I don't know I might be too
much for him
now the new Danny might be too much but
um so no I don't he he makes attempts
for us to get back together but I think
that I'm so far removed from um being in
a relationship just from being hurt you
know when you're when your hurt when
your heart gets broken man it's it's a
hard thing to mend and um I'm currently
not in a relationship I have not been
with anybody since my husband I have no
interest in a relationship I may flirt
or go on a date every now and then but a
relationship is not on my priority list
right
maybe it's a Sagittarius thing because I
feel the same way it's like you got to
focus on the grind yeah I'm so driven
with what I want to do and I'm so
focused on helping my son get on his
feet because my son is my son is a
monster do you think Ryan you think I'm
talented my firstborn son is a beast so
I just you know to help him get his back
on his feet and to to um take this time
to rest and heal is what I've been doing
as of recent but I'm still pushing for
the cushy um I'm still doing comedy I
don't have another show until um New
Year's Eve I'm doing a New Year's Eve
party and in 2017 I plan on going strong
I've um I've gotten involved with a
comedy group um I think we're going to
the Apollo in March um I'm trying to hit
New York I'm also trying to hit
California um I have a couple of
opportunities um at comedy store and uh
the Laugh Factory so I am going to um
follow up on those leads you know 2017
will be a will be more of a a a comedy
and cushy year for me that's right
that's right the cancer is behind me now
so all I have to do is is be uh
proactive and keeping up on my health um
keeping up on my status you know I will
continue to have my
screenings um I'm I will be it's been
four years now so after five years of
being cancer free you are uh less under
the radar you're not under the radar as
much um so it's it's going good I think
it's going good yeah I can see that and
you're busy you're like a Jamaican you
got tree jobs don't you know I know tree
jobs
man so we have this don't you know thing
uh it's an inside joke but um folks she
is a hustler I've never seen someone
hustle so hard in my life she's doing
hair she has a cushy she's a comedian
meeting all these stars and at the end
of the day you know she's still Danny
red wine you know she's a breast cancer
a regular job I work a regular job too I
run a doctor's office so damn damn so
you're you're busy so what do you do for
fun like what is what is what is what's
a day in life with Danny redwind you
know fun for me are things that are not
at my disposal right now you know I
would love to go and be on a beach
somewhere I would love to travel um I
you know that's just in my spirit like I
would love to travel I would love to
eventually live in a warm climate um for
fun usually it's comedy um if I'm not
performing myself I am a big supporter
of my fellow comedians I go to a lot of
shows that I'm not in
um just because I love I love the craft
I love the the comedy so that's what I
do for fun I go to the comedy club and I
hang out with my fellow Comedians and
laugh until my heart is
content come home and probably watch me
some Netflix and eat cookies in bed
that's one of my one of my downfalls
what's your what's your message for all
the women out there that are
entrepreneurs that are going on this
path and they don't know where to start
cuz you know a lot of people since I've
been doing this hustle Zone The Hustle
Zone has been quite successful um uh we
have S sus for example Susan day in the
house that wants to put together an app
and you know there's all kinds of women
that want to make that jump but they're
afraid so what do you tell them I I tell
them you're not you're not going to know
if you don't try um and that's the first
thing if you don't recognize that you
have something that can help others and
you are willing to create that thing and
give to make this world better then then
that's where you need to start none of
us really actually know where to start
like a lot of us have ideas and we don't
really know what to do with those ideas
but you really have to do a little bit
of research you have to do some writing
you have to be disciplined about
spending that time to put together a
business plan or spending that time to
put together what it is that you want to
do um reach out to people um networking
is huge um getting to know people and
other people that are doing things like
you or um things that are kind of on the
same wavelength as far as starting a
business get involved in those things
most cities have um have groups uh you
just have to seek them out um I know
here one of them is grow and it's uh
Grand Rapids um opportunities for women
and they actually help um people start
their own businesses and I know that
they're not the only nonprofit in the
city that helps women start businesses
they have them all over the board it's
just you have to do the research you
have to do the homework the money is out
there I had this one guy tell me he was
like the money is out there it's about
people following through with what it is
that they need to do on their end in
order to get that money they're not just
going to give it to you you have to
follow the right channels you have to do
F fill out whatever necessary paperwork
do whatever it is that they are asking
of you to do in order to get the
resources that you need so my main
advice is don't sit down and let it go
um believe in yourself trust yourself
and go out there and find out what you
need to do to get it done wow you heard
it in the hustle Zone you heard it in
the hustle Zone this is Danny you know
she's not just a pretty face y'all she's
a business woman and she's smart she's
talented and she doesn't give up on
herself doesn't hold grudges because you
can't be successful without you got to
let all that stuff go because you know
and you got to let like one thing when I
first met Danny is that she makes me
feel comfortable you know she makes me
smile she makes everybody smile she
makes everyone laugh you know because
she is herself you know it's so funny
it's like when when you see somebody who
who holds in their light holds in all
the spectrums of themselves and hides it
from people you can tell they're a dark
person you can tell that you don't want
to talk to them you you tell there's
something wrong but when someone just
lets their light
shine you know they bright up
everybody's life it don't matter if
you're in a if you're in in the in in
the deep sea in terms of your emotion
she will like that that light will make
everybody shine as Danny has that light
and I want to thank Danny uh for from
the bottom of my heart this is such a
touching story and I can't wait to see
you on the big screen we're all gunning
for you Danny and
uh I I'm gonna I'm GNA still continue to
promote what you're doing and and talk
about you because again you know you've
gone through everything you've gone
through breast cancer youve you've gone
through a breakup which is hard too
that's like morning you've gone through
um you know being homeless but yet
you you went and you surpass a lot of
comedians that you know are still trying
to get their break that will never see a
Dave Chappelle they'll never get to hang
out with him let alone yeah four hours
ha she like haha yeah that's you better
do that haha CU I mean you got a lot of
things to be proud of so um you know I I
want to thank you again for for coming
in and folks let's let's uh I want to
acknowledge some of the people that are
watching this broadcast so in the
broadcast today we got Horus we got
Susan day we had ke Keegan or not Keegan
Keenan he higs Keenan you know Keenan um
and we got so uh Susan and day we have
um
delandis and uh Kent Johnson everybody's
like cheering you on here so I'm going
to so Susan says I want that you know
she said that um you know know that's me
so she's identifying with this call uh
um cor Corey Smith says what's up sexy
lady okay come
ony um delandis says uh hold on one
second actually no that's not a comment
uh Keegan ke uh Keenan higs sorry I'm
just Lexa Keenan so when I see like when
I see Keenan it like the the the G
exchanges with so it looks like Keegan
so I apologize uh so uh ke Kean says
you're a star Danny the world just
haven't seen it yet and I believe that
wholeheartedly okay so um Horus says she
met Horus online once or twice uh she's
she is cooler than all those people on
blab I guess he's referring to blab
thank you Horus so yeah this is amazing
and again thank you guys all for for
tuning in to the hustle Zone uh and I
hope to like have Danny back you know
maybe we can have a like sometimes I
have Jam sessions where we jam with
other people and just exchange ideas and
stuff like that so um all right we're
going to shut this down but before I go
like I said there is no damn excuse why
you should be sitting there on your
couch doing nothing there's no excuse
why you should be in the dumps there's
no excuse why you should let people in
your life dictate your emotions you are
in control of those emotions you know
every day I wake up and I feel like I
have a reason to live you know instead
of a reason to die you know I I I didn't
like I could identify with not loving
yourself and just putting myself not
eating the right foods not surrounding
myself with the right people not
handling my Affairs my financial affairs
but as soon as you start loving yourself
in its to in your in its totality you
rise above all the odds and Danny is is
definitely a symbol if there was a
dictionary you know her face would be
right there for overcoming for success
for perseverance so you know I'm going
to I like we got to go but welcome to
the hustle Zone The Hustle Zone baby so
thank you guys so much and I will talk
to you guys later hold on one second
then